HA systems used to be extremely hard to build and maintain.
房委会所採用的系统 在建造和保养方面极为困难
These systems were very expensive,
这些系统非常昂贵
relied on custom hardware,
依赖于定制硬件
and required experts to operate them.
并要求专家进行操作
They are used by governments and only a handful of industries such as telecommunications.
它们被政府使用 只有少数几个行业 如电信业
More recently, HA has become more
最近 医管局越来越多
achievable with commodity hardware and open-source software.
可以通过商品硬件和开源软件实现
It still requires extensive time to set up and run.
它仍然需要大量时间来设置和运行
These systems do not need custom hardware,
这些系统不需要定制硬件
they required even more expertise to maintain.
他们需要更多的专业知识来维持
The software was often open-source with no company to provide support.
该软件常常是开源的 没有公司提供支持
Today, in Cloud infrastructures like AWS,
今天 在 AWS 这样的云基础架构中
highly available systems can be set up with a few clicks.
可以通过几次单击来设置高可用性系统
Some knowledge is required to configure and test these systems,
需要一些知识来配置和测试这些系统
but the barrier to entry has been lowered dramatically,
但进入的障碍已经大大降低
opening up these capabilities to far more organizations.
向更多的组织开放这些能力